("Last Nite" by The Strokes)
("Last Nite" continues)
♪ Last night she said ♪
♪ Oh baby I feel so down ♪
♪ Oh it turn' me off
when I feel left out ♪
♪ So I I turned 'round ♪
♪ Oh baby don't care no more ♪
♪ I know this for sure I'm
walking out that door ♪
♪ Well I've been in town
for just about fifteen ♪
♪ Oh minutes now ♪
♪ Oh baby I feel so down
and I don't know why ♪
♪ I keep walking for miles ♪
♪ And see people they don't understand ♪
♪ Your girlfriends they won't understand ♪
♪ Your grandsons they won't understand ♪
♪ And me I aint ever gonna understand ♪
♪ Last night she said ♪
♪ Oh baby don't feel so down ♪
♪ Oh it turn' me off
when I feel left out ♪
♪ So I I turned 'round ♪
♪ Oh baby gonna be just fine ♪
♪ It was a great big lie
'cause I left that night ♪
("Last Nite" continues)
♪ Oh people they don't understand ♪
♪ No girlfriends they won't understand ♪
♪ In spaceships they won't understand ♪
♪ And me I ain't ever gonna understand ♪
♪ Last night she said ♪
♪ Oh baby I feel so down ♪
♪ See it turn' me off
when I feel left out ♪
♪ So I I turned 'round ♪
♪ Oh little girl I don't care no more ♪
♪ I know this for sure I'm
walking out that door yeah ♪
("Last Nite" continues)